

CONTACT

- +598 98 600 681
- Punta Carretas, Mvd, UY
- www.jppuig.netlify.app
- in <u>Juan Pedro Puig</u>

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH ...Highly proficient (CPE)

SPANISHNative

SKILLS

- Languages:
 Java, C++, C#, Python, TypeScript,
 Haskell, Kotlin, SQL, MongoDB
- Other software/tools:
 Relational DB (SQL), non-relation DB
 (MongoDB), Node.js, React, React
 Native, Angular, ASP.NET Core,
 ExpressJs

SOFT SKILLS

- Excellent Communication
- Creative Problem Solving
- Teamwork
- Ability to work under pressure
- Leadership
- Time Management
- Critical Thinking

COURSES

- Innovation and entrepreneurship
- Communication and Leadership (2024)

JUAN PEDRO PUIG

SOFTWARE ENGINEER STUDENT & PROFESSOR

PROFILE

I am a hardworking and enthusiastic college student and professor at Universidad ORT, working towards a degree in Software Engineer. I am a creative problem solver, adept in software development, machine learning and artificial intelligence, fascinated by logic complexity and algorithms.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Universidad ORT, Montevideo

MARCH, 2023 - PRESENT

Associate Professor

- Lecturing and helping students regarding Haskell and C++ for the subjects of Computing Fundamentals and Data Structures and Algorithms 1
- Evaluated and assessed student performance through projects along the semester

Wasabi Digital, Montevideo

MAY, 2021 - SEP, 2022

Paid Media Specialist

- Executed paid social media campaigns that generated an increase in followers and engagement for more than 10 accounts in different teams.
- Brainstorm and application of creative solutions to achieve results
- Analyzed media coverage and social media analytics to measure the success of campaigns and adjust strategies accordingly
- Reference: Martín Gargiulo 095012876

EDUCATION

Universidad ORT

2021 - PRESENT

Software Engineer

Currently on my 7th semester. Three years completed with an average score of 95/100.

Universidad de la República

2019 - 2022

Communications Degree

Three years in studies completed.

Universidad de la República

2016 - 2017

Business Administration Degree

Maristas Zorrilla de San Martín

2010 - 2015

High School